<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>test title</title>
    <description>test description</description>
    <link>test link</link>
    <author>test author</author>
    <item>
      <title>The Papers: Russian exile killed and flats attack fear</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The news that police are treating the death of businessman Nikolai Glushkov as murder leads several papers.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/blogs-the-papers-43438610</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 23:26:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jose Mourinho: Man Utd boss in part two of extraordinary news conference</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Jose Mourinho concludes a remarkable news conference with references to "idiots", "idealists" and the "dictionary of life".]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/43431205</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 22:30:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian Nikolai Glushkov's London death now a murder inquiry</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UK police launch murder investigation after death of Russian businessman Nikolai Glushkov in south-west London]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-43433552</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 22:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Botswana's Ian Khama: Trump encouraging elephant poaching</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Overturning a ban on importing hunting trophies threatens elephants, says Ian Khama.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-africa-43435013</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 22:21:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheltenham Festival: BHA to carry out review after six horse deaths at event</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The British Horseracing Authority is to carry out a review after six horses died at the four-day Cheltenham Festival.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/horse-racing/43438392</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 21:36:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Mini Beast from the East' brings fresh snow warnings</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Met Office warns parts of north-eastern Scotland and England could see up to 20cm of snow.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-43420929</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 21:00:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women's Six Nations: France beat Wales 33-8 to seal Grand Slam</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Watch a selection of France's best tries as they beat Wales 33-8 in their final game of the 2018 Women's Six Nations, sealing the Grand Slam.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/rugby-union/43431209</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:57:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spy poisoning: Putin most likely behind attack - Johnson</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Boris Johnson says Vladimir Putin is "overwhelmingly likely" to have ordered Salisbury attack on ex-spy.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-43429152</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:42:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video assistant referees agreed for World Cup</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Video assistant referees will be used at this year's World Cup, after football's world governing body approves the technology.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/43438344</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:34:02 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six Nations: England women win final match, but miss out on title</title>
      <description><![CDATA[England women comfortably defeat Ireland in their final match of the Six Nations but are denied the title as France beat Wales.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/rugby-union/43401646</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:23:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bacteria found in water at Glasgow Royal Hospital for Children</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Three children are being treated for infections which may be linked to contamination of the water supply.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-scotland-glasgow-west-43438314</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 20:16:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keep it quiet later! Jools in battle with venue next door</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The renowned pianist kept a diary chronicling the "noisy hubbub" outside his Kent country manor.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-kent-43388792</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 19:58:48 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss pianist gives concert on ice in northern Baltic Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Swiss pianist Gabriel Arnold performs for tourists on an icebreaker in Scandinavia's Gulf of Bothnia.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-43437722</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 19:19:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parsons Green attack: Iraqi teenager convicted over Tube bomb</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Ahmed Hassan is found guilty of attempted murder after injuring 30 commuters at Parsons Green.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-43431303</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 18:56:13 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Marauding predator' Jake Killick jailed for sex attacks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The 23-year-old was convicted of rape, sexual assault, false imprisonment and robbery.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-norfolk-43437942</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 18:46:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JFK's never-delivered Dallas speech recreated</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The voice of JFK has been used to reconstruct the speech he was due to deliver on the day he was assassinated.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-scotland-43436361</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 18:35:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James finally finishes Sport Relief Challenge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Radio 1 DJ has completed his Sport Relief Pedal to the Peaks challenge]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-43437119</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 18:23:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The women bringing animated adventures to life</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A record number of women were nominated at the recent British Animation Awards, but men still dominate the industry.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-43437539</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 18:19:20 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six Nations 2018: Ireland face England with Grand Slam in sights</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Ireland need to beat reigning Six Nations champions England at Twickenham to clinch only the third Grand Slam title in their history.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/rugby-union/43434646</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 17:54:04 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheltenham Festival: Native River romps to Gold Cup success</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Native River romps to victory in the Gold Cup at Cheltenham to give Richard Johnson his second victory in the Festival's showpiece race.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/horse-racing/43432064</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 16:57:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mourinho defends record with 12-minute speech</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Watch Manchester United manager Jose Mourinho's extraordinary speech defending his record.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/43429456</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 16:23:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapist caught after urinating in plant pot 30 years later</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Two unsolved rapes were linked to Eric McKenna after police were called to a neighbour dispute.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-tyne-43432662</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 16:17:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skiers jump from speeding lift in Georgia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Several people were injured when the out of control lift started going backwards fast, in Georgia.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-43422186</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 15:38:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Danny Boyle direct the next Bond film? Here's what we know so far</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Slumdog Millionaire director says he's working on the next film with Trainspotting's John Hodge.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-43430301</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 14:53:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Champions League draw: Liverpool face Manchester City in quarter-finals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Manchester City are drawn against Liverpool in an all-Premier League Champions League quarter-final.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/football/43430473</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 14:37:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Life of Pi actor Khan has rare tumour</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Irrfan Khan has acted in over 100 films, including Slumdog Millionaire and The Amazing Spider-Man.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-asia-india-43426481</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 14:28:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four parents who take term-time holidays explain why</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Some say they actively budget for fines, while others believe the penalty system is a "mess".]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-43431173</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 14:22:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger over 'Blackface' makeup segment on Pakistan TV</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A television show darkened models' faces and asked contestants to "transform" them into beautiful brides.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-asia-43429517</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 13:24:12 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fantasist bomber who wanted attention</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Ahmed Hassan came to the UK for "a better life" but used a gift card he won at college to buy bomb-making materials.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-43392551</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 11:32:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child sexual exploitation: How the system failed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Grooming, rape and trafficking are just some of the ways children in the UK are being sexually exploited.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-43400336</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 11:17:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Banksy protest artwork unveiled in New York</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The anonymous artist reveals a new work in New York, drawing attention to a jailed Kurdish painter.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-43428432</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 10:37:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter Paralympics: The explosion that got me to the Paras</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Owen Pick signed up to the Army when he was 16 years old, two years later he would be caught up in an explosion and take up para-snowboarding.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/disability-42890428</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 10:31:23 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Footage of first polar bear cub born in UK in 25 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The "confident and curious" cub was born at Highland Wildlife Park in Kincraig, Scotland.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-43428162</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 08:25:08 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Boyega: Inclusion riders are fantastic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The Star Wars actor tells Newsbeat he's 100% interested in his production company using inclusion riders on future projects]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-43426602</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 07:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poisoned ex-spy: Why does UK think it was Russia?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[The BBC's Gordon Corera considers the attack on Sergei Skripal and his daughter in Salisbury.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-43422184</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 07:00:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracy Beaker is back as a single mum - like these women who grew up in care</title>
      <description><![CDATA[As Tracy returns as an adult, Newsbeat talks to two women who grew up in care and are now single parents.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/newsbeat-43374645</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 02:30:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Integration? It’s about top exam grades’</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Two of England's top schools are Muslim schools in Blackburn. What's their view on integration?]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/education-43420043</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 01:48:42 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UK has 'massive problem' with confident women</title>
      <description><![CDATA["Women shouldn't feel that if they come across as too confident it can be mistaken for arrogance."]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-43401524</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 01:45:39 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A better way to care for dementia patients</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Infrared technology and artificial intelligence offer a better way to take care of dementia patients. It can scan their vital signs 24 hours a day.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-43409215</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:15:11 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to become a professional shopper</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Up to a million people are employed around the world as professional shoppers for clients in China.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-43259904</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:11:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are 'cryonic technicians' the key to immortality?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Freezing the deceased in the hope of one day reviving them could become a mainstream service, advocates say.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-43259902</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:07:50 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I saw Stephen Hawking's death as a disabled person</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Why one disabled BBC journalist has found the reporting of Stephen Hawking's death troubling.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-43418251</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:05:38 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapt or die: How to cope when the bots take your job</title>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first of our Future of Work series, we look at how new tech could change our working lives.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-43259906</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 00:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian spy: Veteran broadcaster fears for UK-Russia relations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Veteran broadcaster Vladimir Posner says UK-Russia relations are the worst he has ever known.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-43424763</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 22:06:27 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several killed, cars crushed in Florida foot bridge collapse</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Six to 10 people were killed when a newly installed pedestrian bridge spanning several lanes of traffic collapsed at Florida International University on Thursday, U.S. Senator Bill Nelson of Florida told local TV station CBS Miami. Emergency personnel searched for signs of life amid the wreckage of concrete, twisted metal and that rained from the collapsed structure and crushed vehicles on one of the busiest roads in South Florida.</p>]]></description>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/article/us-florida-bridge/several-killed-cars-crushed-in-florida-foot-bridge-collapse-idUSKCN1GR2SZ?feedType=RSS&amp;feedName=domesticNews</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 20:51:37 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quiz: The Finns are happy, but who is not?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[7 days quiz: It's the weekly news quiz - have you been paying attention to what's been going on in the world over the past seven days?]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/stories-43418027</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 18:07:14 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mueller witness is convicted pedophile with shadowy past</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>It was a few days before the one-year anniversary of President Donald Trump&#39;s inauguration and a Lebanese-American businessman was on his way to Mar-a-Lago. George Nader, an international fixer whose long history included intrepid back-channel mediation between Israel and Arab countries - and a 15-year-old pedophilia conviction in Europe that has not been previously reported - was transiting through Dulles International Airport outside Washington.</p>]]></description>
      <link>https://www.agassizharrisonobserver.com/news/mueller-witness-is-convicted-pedophile-with-shadowy-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 16:22:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US accuses Russia of hacking energy grid, imposes sanctions for election meddling</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Trump administration accused Russia on Thursday of a concerted, ongoing operation to hack and spy on the U.S. energy grid and other critical infrastructure, and separately imposed sanctions on Russian officials for alleged high-tech interference in the 2016 American presidential election. U.S. national security officials said the FBI, the Homeland Security Department and American intelligence agencies determined that Russian intelligence and others were behind the attacks on the energy sector.</p>]]></description>
      <link>https://www.ocregister.com/2018/03/15/us-accuses-russia-of-hacking-energy-grid-imposes-sanctions-for-election-meddling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 15:55:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'I tried to kill myself nine times before the NHS helped me'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[At the age of 17 Sherry Denness tried to kill herself nine times in 10 days, and only then got the help she needed.]]></description>
      <link>http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/stories-43227589</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 03:07:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bay Area members of Congress move to protect work permits for H-1B visa holdersa spouses</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Six Bay Area members of Congress have signed onto a letter asking the Department of Homeland Security to scrap a plan to prevent spouses of H-1B visa holders from obtaining work permits. The department in December announced the plan , citing President Donald Trump&#39;s "Buy American and Hire American" executive order, and said it would carry out the plan this year.</p>]]></description>
      <link>https://www.eastbaytimes.com/2018/03/14/bay-area-members-of-congress-move-to-protect-work-permits-for-h-1b-visa-holders-spouses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 02:34:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
